If you fail to stop me, the world
will come to an end, Great Hero.
So this is all I've got?
Enough with the cheap moves.
Let's settle things once and for all.
You and me, going all out.
Very well.
I couldn't ask for more.
Dragon Series, Fifth Sword.
Satanic power at full force.
Be reduced to ashes!
Dragon Annihilator!
It's finally over...
Good morning!
Oh, you're here.
Oh! They're greeting each other!
Is that what friends do?!
Good morning!
Morning. You're here early.
I see! This is what normal people do!
All right!
Starting today, I'm going to make friends
and live life as an ordinary person!
Episode 1
Earnest
Okay! Time to make some friends!
Good morning!
Good morning! Good morning!
Pretty funny student we've got here.
Do you think he's a new transfer?
Whoa, he's coming this way!
I'm Blade!
Ah, yes.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Blade!
You sure are a weirdo.
I'm Kassim.
My name's Clay. Nice to meet you.
I'm Yessica.
Oh, um... I'm Claire.
I see!
I'm here to make some friends!
If you don't mind, would you
like to be friends with us?
I did it!
I've got four whole friends now!
If this keeps up, I could make ten friends...
No, hold that thought!
Even 100 friends doesn't sound so far-fetched!
If you want to make 100 friends,
you'll have to befriend the whole student body.
What are all of you up to?
Why are you making a commotion
in the middle of the hallway?
Oh, no!
You are all students at the
prestigious Rosewood Academy.
That's Earnest Flaming.
You should strive to always follow the
rules and behave in an orderly manner.
She's the top student in this school,
so everyone calls her the Empress.
I'm Blade!
Who are you?
I haven't seen you around here.
U-Um, Lady Earnest...
No need for the title!
Well, it seems Blade just
transferred into the school...
A new student?
This academy only admits those who aspire
to be heroes who protect this world!
There's no way they'd permit
such a late admission!
I don't really care about being a hero.
I'm just here to make some friends.
You don't really care?!
What halfhearted resolve you have!
Oh, almost forgot!
I need to go to the headmaster's office!
What?!
Can you show me the way to
the headmaster's office?
Go!
Why'd it have to be me?
This is Earnest Flaming.
I'm here with a brat who lost his
way and was on the verge of tears.
You may enter.
Pardon me.
Wh-What brings you here, Sir?!
I'm here!
Y-You idiot!
Don't you have any idea
who you stand before?!
Sure I do.
Please forgive his rudeness,
Your Majesty the King!
I've heard all about you from the
previous headmaster, Miss Earnest.
It seems you have quite the excellent record.
O-Oh, no. I have a long way to go...
Excuse me, "previous headmaster"?
Indeed.
As of today, I will be acting
as the new headmaster here.
Your Majesty is?!
Why, I hear Your Majesty is
quite the accomplished warrior!
To be instructed by Your Majesty himself!
I find myself lacking words to
express my joy at the sheer honor!
I could never have imagined I would get
a chance to speak with Your Majesty!
How can I put this?
Oh, I really am so truly struck with awe!
That's enough.
Huh?
You may take your leave.
I must speak with him in private.
What's the deal with that boy?!
He's so friendly with His Majesty!
I don't get it!
Hey! Thanks to you,
I've gotten on her bad side!
What could be the reason?
Don't give me that!
And what are you doing here, anyway?!
You see, Blade...
I want you to regain your powers as a hero.
I want to be an ordinary person!
Normal as can be!
The students here are really something.
They should serve well
in your rehabilitation.
You're not listening, old man.
I plan on making sweeping changes
to the curriculum, as well.
My predecessor had a bit of a lenient streak.
We're trying to nurture heroes here.
Great heroes like you—
There's no need for that!
The Demon King's gone now.
I received reports of the Great Hero
and the Demon King trading blows,
resulting in mutual annihilation
of their powers.
That's right.
But I have faith!
The Great Hero's powers will be resurrected!
And that's because you are the Great Hero!
This old man's gone off the deep end.
Hey!
Why are you here?
This is the advanced class!
I took the exam for the lower classes,
but I was told to come here.
Did you bribe someone?!
What?
Did you gain back-door
admission into this school?!
You must have cheated somehow to be
placed straight into the advanced class!
Besides, this isn't the kind of academy
that admits halfhearted people like you!
Don't call me halfhearted!
I'm dead serious.
About making 100 friends here.
What?
I'm Blade!
Let's be friends!
What?
I'm Blade!
Wh-What do you want?
Let's be friends!
I'm Blade!
Listen to me!
I'm listening.
D-Don't pat my head!
Whoa.
The instructor has asked
everyone to assemble.
I'll be right there.
I'm Blade!
He's asking for your name.
Is that a command?
She's always like this.
I'm Blade!
You need to listen when people are talking.
Sophie.
I see!
I'm Blade!
Nice to meet you!
Instructor!
Wh-What is it?
I'd like to test the
transfer student's ability.
Well, that wasn't in today's lesson plan...
You don't mind, right?
Go ahead...
That's made of enchanted metal, right?
And what if it is?
Just so you know,
simply slicing through it is something
all the advanced students can do.
Your job is to prove yourself
to everyone here.
If you can't, I'll have you admit to your
illicit entry and leave the academy.
The advanced class is on
a whole different level.
How many levels are we talking?
Huh? W-Well... two...
No, three!
It's three whole levels different!
I see. Three levels, huh?
Then, Second Sword should do.
Wait, the shape of his fighting spirit...
Dragon Series?!
Dragon Series? Wait!
Dragon Eater!
Cough.
Hmm... Meh.
Blade.
Who in the world... are you?
I-I'm ordinary!
Just your exceedingly average,
ordinary person!
Ordinary... Ordinary?!
No, the best thing they
serve is their hamburger!
Hey!
Seriously, what's your deal?
Like I said, I'm just ordinary.
And that's why she messed up!
What, for real?
Hey! There are seats here!
Hey! Over here!
What's gotten into them?
This table is basically reserved for me.
Wait... are you being bullied?
You can talk to me about it.
You're a real moron.
Everyone's scared of me.
Scared of you? Why?
Whoa, what is this?!
I'm not sure what it is, but it's great!
Huh? It's just curry.
Tonkatsu curry.
So it's called tonkatsu curry?!
Tonkatsu curry is super amazing!
The guy who invented it was a real genius!
I take back what I said about you.
What was that again?
I mean when I accused you
of illicit entry here!
Did you say that?
I sure did!
It's been bothering me,
and you don't even remember?!
Since I don't remember,
you shouldn't let it bother you.
I admit you've got a bit of talent.
So, well...
I'm sorry.
Did you say something?
I swear! You're so...
You have my thanks.
You've done so much to help me.
Wh-What's this all of a sudden?!
I'm a new transfer, right?
I thought I wouldn't be
able to make any friends.
Huh? Friends? Who?
Wait, m-me?!
Yeah.
Look, we're eating lunch together.
That makes us pals!
W-Well, I don't mind being your friend...
That was easy.
The Empress is so quick to fall.
Seriously, what's with him?
Eating together makes you friends?
How absurd.
Friends, he said...
Yay!
My very first friend!
Surrender yourself to me.
Destroy! Slash! Burn!
Shut up!
I'm the next head of the Flaming family!
I won't give in to the likes of you!
Leonard, take this fight seriously!
Dear me.
We may be simulating a real fight,
but I'd rather not wield
my lance against a lady!
Wow! So awesome!
Come! It's time for this show to begin!
How merciless.
It seems I've lost.
Earnest?
The Empress has been kind of scary lately.
Next!
If you continue this...
I admit defeat.
You're up next, Blade!
Huh, me?
That Dragon Series of yours
is no big deal if I dodge it!
I mean, I don't mind.
But will you be all right in that condition?
Shut up!
I'll be fine.
Let's go!
Oh, no!
Hey, Earnest!
There's nothing I can do.
Don't say that!
Make her better, like you did for me!
I can heal diseases and injuries,
even from the brink of death.
But spells and curses are
outside of my expertise.
Where am I?
You passed out.
Don't you remember?
I...
Don't tell me...
Just calm down!
Did I... um... do something?
Something really awful?
Really awful?
No, you just suddenly fell unconscious.
Oh, it was really awful carrying you here.
Y-You dummy!
I'm not that heavy!
You should rest a little longer.
That affliction of yours...
Stop it!
I feel better now.
No. Get back in bed.
Out of my way.
I'm not budging.
It seems like Earnest feels okay,
so why not let her go?
I'll keep an eye on her instead.
Fine.
That's a promise.
Seriously?
I can walk on my own.
You can lean on me, you know.
We're friends, after all.
Don't tell anyone what you
heard in the infirmary.
Looks like I owe that old man now.
Not that I mind.
There we go.
Rosewood Academy's data...
So that demon sword's name is Asmodeus?
Dunno why, but it gives me the creeps.
Quiet down.
I see now.
Why do you want to talk in private?
Are you trying to threaten me?
Huh?
Why would I threaten you?
Maybe you want my spot as top student.
I couldn't care less about that.
What's more important is you.
I'm interested in you.
What?!
Wait, that's, well...
I said we could be friends,
but anything more is...
I know the secret behind your sword.
That sword has its own will,
and grants its owner tremendous power.
But you don't have full ownership of it.
How did that happen?
When I was six years old,
I unknowingly laid my hands on a cursed
demon sword in the Flaming family's custody.
It tried to take over my body
and the demon sword's will flowed through me,
hungering for blood and carnage.
Ever since, I've been
holding back those urges.
As soon as I let my guard down,
I can hear it still, to this day.
The voice of Asmodeus,
begging me to let it slash and burn.
But it hasn't taken over.
No.
Thanks to my stubbornness.
There is a way.
I know that much.
I need the demon sword to
acknowledge me as its owner, right?
But I can't do that.
What if I fail?
Then a bloodthirsty demon would come to life!
It'll be okay.
What?!
How can you say something so irresponsible?!
If the demon comes to life...
Like I said, it'll be okay.
What?
If that happens, I'll cut it down.
That's...
Don't think I can do it?
I think you can.
So what's the problem?
Nothing at all.
Demon Sword Asmodeus!
I am Earnest Flaming.
I beseech thee to form a pact with me!
Obey thy oath from days bygone,
and receive my being within thy own!
Try my strength.
See if thou can consume me!
So be it.
I have faith in you, Earnest.
I have faith as well,
that you'll bring this all to an end,
no matter what happens.
So you must be Asmodeus.
I'll keep it brief.
Submit yourself to me.
I am fire!
I am power!
I am pure violence that
reigns over all destruction!
Looks like it means a fight, then.
Bring it on!
Destroy, destroy, destroy!
Kill, kill, kill!
Burn, burn, burn!
Oh, what fun!
I don't want to hold back!
Not when there's so much
to destroy around me!
My house, my family, my friends!
That's right.
I can fight now, thanks to him.
Even if I fail, I know he'll take it down.
Which is why I'll fight,
of my own will.
For the sake of my own pride!
My name...
My name is Earnest!
Earnest Flaming!
I made it back.
Welcome back.
What, really?
Yeah! And then Kassim was like...
Good morning.
Does it look weird on me?
You look quite splendid!
Uh-huh!